internetdj.com 2007-05-02

# Privacy Statement for InternetDJ.com

InternetDJ is committed to providing quality online activities and information to fans. While we encourage the interactive nature of online media, we strive to ensure the online safety and privacy of our visitors. 

Information Collection Policies We may request personally identifiable information from visitors who choose to participate in certain activities as described below. Our information practices are described below. 

Third Party Advertising  
We use MaxOnline and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please click [here](http://www.maxonline.com/privacy_policy/index.php). 

Third Party Cookies  
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser. 

General Activities 

Online Sweepstakes and Contests  
From time to time, InternetDJ offers visitors the opportunity to enter sweepstakes or contest for a prize. InternetDJ may ask for information such as name and e-mail address. InternetDJ uses this information only for purpose of conducting the sweepstakes or contest and does not disclose such information to third parties, except with a fulfillment house that InternetDJ may contract to help select winners and fulfill prizes. Once the sweepstakes or contest is finished, InternetDJ deletes the personal information collected on the online entry forms. 

E-mail  
InternetDJ provides visitors the opportunity to send e-mail to us. We request no personally identifiable information from the visitor. We may share e-mail addresses with our affiliated departments and businesses that may have their own disclosure practices. Visitors' e-mail correspondences are deleted from our system periodically. 

Electronic Postcards  
InternetDJ may give visitors the option to send "electronic postcards" to friends. We ask the visitor to submit the first name and e-mail addresses of their friends. InternetDJ uses this information only for the purpose of sending the postcards. The recipient's e-mail address is deleted periodically from our system. 

Use of Information  
At InternetDJ, we may share aggregate information about our visitors with both our affiliated businesses (e.g. Dashboard Music Group, LLC) and externally with third parties, such as advertisers and business partners. We may also share personal information about our visitors (e.g. email address) with our affiliated departments and businesses that may have their own disclosure practices. However, it is our policy to not disclose externally with third parties personal information collected on our site, except in the following instances: 

Agents  
The personal information provided to InternetDJ by visitors may be transferred, disclosed or shared with third parties who may be engaged by us specifically to handle and deliver certain activities (e.g., sweepstakes) and perform other technical and processing functions, such as sending e-mail, providing user services to our visitors, or otherwise operating our site. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes. 

Business Transfers  
In the event that all or substantially all of the assets relating to InternetDJ are transferred or sold to another entity, personally identifiable information may be transferred to the acquiring entity. 

Special Cases  
We may also disclose personally identifiable information to third parties when required by law or is pertinent to judicial or government investigations or proceedings, or otherwise necessary to protect our Web site or the safety of its users. Other than as set forth above, we do not at present intend to use your personal information for other purposes. However, in the future we may disclose personal information you have provided to third parties for additional purposes and in the event we do, we will provide notices of such use to our users. 

Cookies and Log Data   
Cookies are information files that your web browser places on the hard drive of your computer when you visit a web site. Cookies cannot damage user files, nor can they read information from a user's hard drive. Cookies allow web sites to "remember" users activities on a web site as well as users visits to a site. At InternetDJ, cookies are used to determine the number of unique visitors to our web site over a given period. We do not store any personal information into cookies nor do we link or combine information collected through cookies to any personal information submitted by users when participating in our activities. Log data collected on web servers both within InternetDJ's control and under the control of internetdj.com's third party ad service provider, who is required to maintain such data on a confidential basis, supplies InternetDJ with aggregate information about the number of visits to different pages on our site. InternetDJ uses such aggregate information to improve access to our content based on our visitors' browsers and operating system types to make our content available to as many users as possible. We do not link the "log data" collected to personally identifiable information submitted by users when participating in our activities. 

Security  
InternetDJ has taken steps to ensure that personally identifiable information collected is secure, including limiting the number of people who have physical access to our database servers as well as electronic security systems and password protections, which guard against unauthorized access. 

Questions/Concerns?  
If you have any questions regarding InternetDJ's privacy policy, please contact us at:   
InternetDJ.com   
17 State Street  
12th Floor  
New York, New York 10004 

This policy, like the online medium itself, is subject to change. 

### Article Comments

 _ **No comments found for this article**_  

### Post Your Comment

**You need to be logged in** in order to post your comments. 

**Click Here** to login or register if you don't have an account.
